hey what's up Jeremiah Kowski here
listen if you are a coach Mentor trainer
you're trying to get more clients online
I want to show you the best funnel that
you can use that'll work for you to get
clients to sell your courses to sell
your trainings to sell your memberships
for those of you I haven't met yet I've
been in this coaching mentoring and
training space for over 21 years I've
scaled multiple businesses to over $10
million a year in profit I personally
built coaching businesses over $10
million a year in profit and I want to
show you what's working around right now
what we're doing right now with our
clients we're actually spending
literally uh close to $100,000 in
advertising Behind these ideas that I'm
going to be sharing with you right now
okay so when it comes to getting clients
in your coaching or training
business it's all about getting the
right people at the right time in front
of you for a presentation and you want
to build trust with people and if you're
a coach or you're a mentor who wants to
be able to get more clients you have to
learn how to effectively build trust
with people most people don't know how
to do this they don't know the best way
to do this and there's way too many
ideas that are out there that they get
all jumbled up and so by the end of this
video I'm going to be sharing with you
the simplest strategy that you can use
that you can apply to get more clients
in your coaching training or course
business okay so everything starts with
the fact that people are out here we
call this The Ether
okay and what the e ether is is this is
where people that you don't know who
they are exist all right you never met
them before they could be on social
media they could be on somebody's
podcast they could be on YouTube and so
this is like
unrefined uh raw information as far as
people goes what you have to do is you
have to find a way to get their
attention and then get them to come into
your ecosystem
and so if you are a coach trainer or
mentor and you want to get people to
become a client of yours you have to get
them in front of you so that you can
build trust with them about the fact
that you can solve their problems people
are looking for
transformation okay and so you're taking
people from
attention to transformation and there's
a process in the middle of this the very
best method and a lot of people can call
this attraction marketing I've actually
seen somebody called it strategic
seduction I thought that's not quite how
I would say it but it gets the point
across you need something that is
enticing to the pool of people that are
out here okay so you got a pool of
people that exist out here that have the
potential of working with you and so you
have to create something that entices
them and gets their interest to spend
time with you now this is you over here
this is you
turning them into a client right here
okay and Beyond turning them into a
client right you're bringing results
transformation you're changing their
lives they're experiencing what it's
like to become a client of yours they're
they're they're loving it this is where
the testimonies come from okay so how do
we bridge that
gap between these two you have people
that are out there the pool of people
and then you have them becoming a client
and right here is the the land of I
don't know what the heck I'm doing
basically where where most people are
right is how do we get them from here to
here right it should be an easy path but
it's not and so what your opportunity is
is this this where you want to spend
about 80% of your time okay most coaches
and mentors actually spend most of their
time 80% of their time in coaching and
mentoring clients you want to spend
about 20% of your time and actually
coaching and mentoring your clients and
if you actually want to build a business
that's going to be making you multiple
six and even seven figures and we built
businesses up to that level and so what
you got to do is you got to become a
master at Bridging the Gap between where
people are to where they want to be and
where you want them to be as well and
that's where you're going to spend about
80% of your time is actually bridging
that Gap with people right here okay so
that means that you're going to spend
time time connecting with people
building trust with them showing them
what it is that you have to offer and
then bringing them into your ecosystem
great example in my business this video
right here because you have you haven't
you didn't pay for this video right
you're watching it for free okay is part
of my 80% of the time of where I connect
with people to build trust with them and
and I and I know that out of that group
of people some people will become
clients mine now here's the thing you
don't have to create a bunch of YouTube
videos you don't have to create a bunch
of content on social media you just need
one simple path to get people to become
a client ears and that's by creating
a
lead magnet and I'm sure you've heard
the term lead magnet before but what a
lead magnet is is it's basically an
onramp from the pool of people over here
to coming into your ecosystem and
getting
into your funnel if you think about a
highway when people are driving along a
highway to get from point A to point B
they are getting funneled in from all of
the different homes that they're at
around their City to get to their
destination and the destination might be
In-N-Out cheeseburger who knows you know
or or MAD Greens if you're vegetarian
right I love both of the places they're
great Inn out MAD Greens both of them
are good just depends on what mood I'm
going going for okay but when I leave my
home I'm leaving and I'm funneling onto
the highway to get there and that's
exactly what you're doing is you are
funneling people onto the
highway it's the idea of a highway and
and actually a road system is actually
far more
accurate than even a funnel is
technically and so what your lead magnet
is is your lead magnet is the is the
path that they take your lead magnet is
like when people type it into their
Google Maps as far as that goes so
people are looking for something
specific to solve a problem that they
have now when it comes to you as a coach
or a course creator or a trainer okay
there's a lot of people that are out
there that might do the things that you
do you might have a lot of competition
that's out there okay you don't want to
worry about the competition first off
you want to focus on who are the people
that I can help the most with the things
and the problems that I solve and then
one of the things very specifically that
they want solved that I can deliver on
okay now if you don't know what that is
I have a training in my YouTube channel
where I show you how to find your Niche
you can look that up go look up my name
and find your Niche and if you want to
work with me deeper on this in my
coaching program the client growth
accelerator we work with people to
create multi-million doll funnels I
become part of your team and join you to
help you do this and put all of this
together okay so what you want to do is
you want to figure out of the people
that you're connecting with that are out
here not everybody is a good
fit okay not everybody is a good fit to
go on a date with not everybody's a good
fit to be a friend and not everybody's a
good fit to be a client not everybody on
YouTube that exists is a good fit to
become a client of mine because I'm not
desperate and I'm not needing to be
desperate and that's one of the things
you want to lay down desperation lay
down that need for people to become
clients of yours if internally you're
like agitated and anxious needing people
to become clients that comes across and
people are like oh wow this this
person's kind of needy uh I don't know
if I want to work with them and then
what ends up happening is the people who
do want to work with you they're also
way needier and they're just nightmare
clients in general it's just that just
doesn't work okay so what we want to do
is we want to become confident in the
fact that we got something amazing and
incredible to deliver to people and
we're going to bring them into our
ecosystem so we figure out what are
their deepest desires okay remember I
mentioned creating something that's
enticing something that is seductive
something that is attractive it
attraction okay so what is their desires
what are they salivating about the more
and and that ties directly to those
words that I just used what do they
really really want
more than anything else that just lights
their
fire do you know what it
is once you do you create a lead magnet
around that specific
thing now you may not know exactly what
that is that's where artificial
intelligence can be very valuable to be
able to brainstorm and come up with
ideas for how to figure out what some of
those are you can ask ask chat GPT
prompts to help you come up with ideas
for what people want but one of the best
things to do is you can actually
literally survey and pull people you get
them into your ecosystem and you start
to ask them questions you start to
create opportunities to answer their
questions and then the more people that
you work with you get to answer their
questions and then by answering those
questions of those people you figure out
exactly what people's desires
are and so once you figure out what
those desires are you can create
something that's packaged it doesn't
take a long time to do this very simple
funnel that gives them exactly what they
want okay so that's going to be stage
number one is you want to actually
create something whether it be a video
training whether it be a a webinar
whether it be a recording whether it be
a master class whether it be a live
event I personally love doing webinars
and Live Events it's one of my favorite
ways of doing things like that and what
we get to do is during that we're not
going to bring transformation to people
I want you to understand this okay we're
not bringing transformation to people
these are purely methods of marketing
again this video right here is the
perfect example of what I mean by this
me making this video I am I'm giving you
value I'm giving you the blueprint but
I'm not taking 10 to 12 hours to spend
time with you and bring ultimate
transformation to your life like this is
this is going to this is going to be
helpful for you but this video alone is
not going to just transform everything
for you it's a it's a piece of the
puzzle okay so that's what you want to
do is you want to figure out what is one
piece of your puzzle that you deliver to
people and then you create something
around that that people can sign up with
their name and email address for and
then you deliver that in the form of
video content okay and we these are
presentations that have value inside of
them but also you're selling something
now in this video I'm not actually
selling anything at all there's no sales
pitch at the end of this I'm not even
going to give you an offer other than
I'd love to see you in my accelerator
program at some point you can find the
link below super simple okay as far as
you knowing what to create a lead magnet
around it has to be tied to the deepest
desire that your prospect has okay so
whatever they desire
this might be your coaching program or
your course right here right we have a
course or a program
okay your prospect's deepest desire
might be right here and they might even
have different
desires and so what you can do is these
become roads that lead people to your
program as far as that goes okay so you
figure out what are those desires that
people have do they want to learn how to
run Facebook ads do they want to know
how to start a course do they want to
know uh how to host a webinar as far as
that goes when it comes to the content
that I create do they want to do they
want to know how to how to generate more
leads or grow their email list right
when it comes to the content that I
create these are all a lot of the hooks
that I that I like to use because these
are the main desires that people have
initially that they want to figure out
and so we use those as entry points to
bring people in so even though my system
right here it's a complete all
encompassing system that solves all of
these problems for people and makes them
a ton of money when they start to apply
it what I'm going to do is the entry
point is going to cover just one piece
of the puzzle I'm not trying to give
people everything that I have to offer
in that one piece okay so I figure out
what that one piece is
and then I start to go find people that
are out on the internet through social
media to be able to do this okay so
there's a couple of ways that we can do
this through social media we can create
a we can create short form video content
like Instagram reels and in those
Instagram reels we share something that
is related to what that offer is over
here so we have two offers we have our
lead magnet offer and we have our paid
offer and then what we do is we bring
people in to the lead magnet offer using
an Instagram reel that's then going to
lead them to this now you can actually
run ads to these Instagram reels and get
people to sign up for your lead magnet
offer okay now here's the deal people
might not sign up right away just
because they joined your lead magnet and
this is the beautiful part about this
system okay so the goal
is in all of this you want to grow
your email list no matter what you're
doing you want to increase your email
list you want to add more people to your
email list because what you can do is
you can send
them YouTube video content if you have
it you can send
them Instagram video content you can
send them webinars you can send them
events so if somebody signs up through a
lead
magnet and they don't become a client
you can continue to email them
additional pieces of content that you
have and this creates a nurturing
process where you're starting to
overtime build trust maybe from a level
one to a level three to a level five to
a level 10 once they hit a level 10 they
are ready to jump in
and become a
client and so your goal is once they're
on your email list you are continuing to
nurture that connection with them you're
continuing to build that relationship
over time with them with different forms
of content that you deliver okay now
here's where it becomes very easy and
simple number one we have the access to
so much information on YouTube on
Instagram on Tik Tok and with our
artificial intelligence as well as
Amazon and we use all of these as market
research tools to figure out what are
the best topics to be able to create
offers around so like what I can look at
is I can look at if there's other people
that are in my space What are the top
videos that they might be creating on
YouTube by the way this video right here
literally I did a 10 minutes of
research and that's how I actually came
up with the idea to make this video
because I know a my market wants this
the people that are doing similar to
what I offer in the marketplace have
videos similar to this and so that's why
I'm going to be sending this to my email
list out there people are going to be
able to watch this they're going be able
to check it out and that's going to
start ranking and they're going to
they're going to start I'm going to
start building trust with people from
that okay so I'm not looking to
necessarily close a sale at every single
one of these but I'm always going to
mention what I have to offer okay now
when you do this one of the things that
you want to make sure of is that in your
lead magnet you want to have a direct
sales message okay you want to have some
kind of messaging where you're going to
be inviting people with an ask to become
a client of yours if you don't do that
people are just going to disappear off
into the ether so the idea is that as
soon as they join your email list
something that they have to register
for they know that you have something
for sale as far as that goes okay so you
have something for sale you have
something that they know that you're
offering that's already in their mind
and so now when you can show up in front
of them with these different forms of
content and ways that you're building
trust with them
they're thinking about the fact that oh
I want to become a client of yours over
here but I want to test you out I want
to try you out I want to check out with
this like I want to go on a second date
and a third date and a fourth date with
you and and eventually maybe they will
seal the deal and and you know get
married to you what it's not what I'm
talking about but I'm talking about you
know they become a client to yours as
far as that goes and so but you want
that to happen on their timeline and
this is where attraction marketing works
best now you want to be direct with your
intentions you don't want to hide those
you want you don't want to Veil your
intentions
that's like friend zoning your clients
it's not a good thing to do okay you you
want to be very upfront about your
intentions and that alone actually will
make you a lot more money because you're
not trying to hide the fact that you
have something for sale I'm not hiding
the fact at all in this video that I
have a coaching program that I would
love to see you a part of get it and so
but in that you're also not being pushy
about that fact when you go on a date
with some somebody you're you're not
hiding the fact that hey you know I'd
like to take this
further but you're also not pushing the
issue but you're you're moving the
needle forward and that's the kind of
energy that you want to have inside of
your sales funnels as you want as you
want it to attract people to go from
stage to Stage to Stage to Stage to
Stage okay so when people sign up to
your email list what you're going to do
is you're going to follow up with them
with the piece of content that you have
this is one of the of the things that I
noticed that a lot of people don't do is
they don't follow up so if somebody
signs up for some piece of content with
you they're joining your email list
maybe they join for some kind of a
webinar some kind of a training right
here
okay you want to send
them one two
three over the course of three days
emails to them reminding them of what
they sign sign up for maybe it's a
replay that you're able to give them as
far as that goes okay and so by doing
this you're re-engaging them for the
first thing that they signed up for then
after that you can send them all of your
other emails that you have to them so
that
then you stay engaged with them so
you're keeping them informed about what
your offer is you're letting them know
about the opportunity to become a client
of yours you could use something like
dead line funnel which actually has a
countdown a limited amount of time that
they can sign up for your paid offer
attached to
this and if they don't buy it during
that time you just Loop them right back
into other pieces of content other
offers we can run retargeting ads with
other offers that we have and that keeps
people engaged in buying into it okay
and so again if you want to talk about
like what's the best funnel uh platforms
or things like that there's a lot of
different ones out there I personally
use Squarespace I found it to be super
easy to use as far as that goes uh go
high level is another great one systemi
IO is free uh don't get caught up in the
weeds of what what technology or
platform to use understand that a funnel
is not a platform it's a blueprint and
it's a method of taking people from the
pool of people that are out there to
getting them into your space so that you
can make a presentation to them build
trust with them and show them ultim Ely
the value that you have to deliver to
them okay if you want to start to
implement this and put this into your
business I'd love to work with you to be
able to do this one of the biggest
things that we actually help people with
inside of my program is we walk you
through the entire process
of finding your
[Music]
Niche we help you dial in your
advertising campaigns we help you hone
in your sales process as well as your
messaging and sales copy all of your
emails all the marketing all the funnels
all of that we help you put all of those
together so that you have
consistent
income so that you
have
massive
impact and so that ultimately you have
total CL
clarity about what steps to take in your
business which lead to having
time
and
Financial Freedom in your life and so if
you want that if you want to work with
us to be able to do all of that and
bring all that together to help you put
your business together again I'd love
for you to join me in my client growth
accelerator program go check it out and
I'll talk to you soon make sure you
subscribe to the channel have a good one
everybody